[
     {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 41?",
      "correctAnswer": "1681",
      "options": [
        "1683",
        "1681",
        "1679",
        "1686"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 66?",
      "correctAnswer": "4356",
      "options": [
        "4361",
        "4358",
        "4356",
        "4354"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 30?",
      "correctAnswer": "900",
      "options": [
        "900",
        "902",
        "905",
        "898"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 41?",
      "correctAnswer": "1681",
      "options": [
        "1686",
        "1683",
        "1681",
        "1679"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 77?",
      "correctAnswer": "5929",
      "options": [
        "5931",
        "5927",
        "5929",
        "5934"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 49?",
      "correctAnswer": "2401",
      "options": [
        "2399",
        "2403",
        "2406",
        "2401"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 13?",
      "correctAnswer": "169",
      "options": [
        "169",
        "167",
        "174",
        "171"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 71?",
      "correctAnswer": "5041",
      "options": [
        "5046",
        "5043",
        "5041",
        "5039"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 59?",
      "correctAnswer": "3481",
      "options": [
        "3483",
        "3481",
        "3479",
        "3486"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 51?",
      "correctAnswer": "2601",
      "options": [
        "2606",
        "2603",
        "2599",
        "2601"
      ]
    }
]